Everybody poops
Everybody poops in holes
Some covered by porcelain thrones
Some are nothing but dirt and stones
Some seats are heated
Some seats are gold-plated, sanitized and treated
Some don’t have seats, you just gotta squat
That’s just what you got
Everybody poops
From kings in their marble rooms
To kids in their light-up shoes
No matter what you own
You’re still alone
When nature calls the truth
Everybody poops
Not everybody uses toilet paper wipes
Some use water jets
Others use rocks
Some just improvise
Some are terrible
Some are easy
Some are splashy
Some are breezy
Some take time
Some won’t stop
Some you pray just drop
Everybody poops
From penthouse views to camping loops
From fancy spa to forest roots
No matter what you prove
No matter what you choose
We all pay nature’s dues
Everybody poops
It doesn’t care who you are
It doesn’t care what you make
It doesn’t care about your car
Or the promises you break
When the moment comes
There’s no escape
Everybody poops
In silver stalls or muddy boots
It humbles presidents and brutes
You can laugh or you can mope
But there’s no way to elope
From the oldest human truth
Everybody poops
Poops